<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title>Ethan Hsu</title>
 <link href="/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="http://localhost:4000/"/>
 <updated>2023-07-06T12:34:49-04:00</updated>
 <id>http://localhost:4000</id>
 <author>
   <name>Ethan Hsu</name>
   <email></email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>How is this website built</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2023/06/29/on-the-website/"/>
   <updated>2023-06-29T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2023/06/29/on-the-website</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;motivation&quot;&gt;Motivation&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve always wanted to build a website before. When I was doing frontend developing
for a project, I thought about writing one in &lt;abbr&gt;ReactJS&lt;/abbr&gt;. However, it
seems overkill to write a static website with it, but I also don’t want to simply
copying down templates and add my own text.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recently, I learned that a lot of Ph.D. students and Professors use Jekyll to
simplify the making of their websites. I thought it was a good idea to learn
the framework, so here we are!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;technical-details&quot;&gt;Technical Details&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The website is powered by Jekyll, I cloned the structure of existing &lt;a href=&quot;https://cvless.netlify.app/&quot;&gt;template&lt;/a&gt;
online. This greatly reduced the time needed for me to import icons and writing
CSS from scratch. Under this structure, I add my own JavaScript and CSS to
build the website. I am still testing out different things and adding more content.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;to-dos&quot;&gt;To-dos&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am planning to add a detail section of my education and coursework, potentially
I might even add a brief comments of each course I’ve taken in college.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also find it hard to organize my past projects because I never really dedicated
a large amount of time to a single project. Usually my way of learning is to
build new things from existing works (class homework) or taking courses with
final projects. With this website, it might be easier to share things that I did.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!-- ## Roadmaps --&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 

</feed>
